madhuloka.com 2013-11-12

# :: Madhuloka ::

Privacy Notice

#### About Privacy:

**Will Madhuloka.com disclose any of my personal information?**

Madhuloka will not disclose any of your personal information, except when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, or to protect the rights or property of Madhuloka. 

**Will Madhuloka use my information for direct mailings?**

Yes, but only if you give us permission. We will send you information about our various products and promotions we feel may be of interest to you. Only Madhuloka will send you these direct mailings. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply tell us when you give us your personal information. Or, at any time you can easily remove your name from our list through the My Account page so you no longer receive such offers and mailings. 

**What else should I know about my privacy?**

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through email, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online. 

#### About Security:

This is a secure site and all personal information is not transmitted by e-mail. 

Why sometimes your browser says that you are being redirect to an unsecure page? After you place an order, we send you back to our home page. The order form is secure, and the regular site pages aren't. Whenever you redirect from a secure to an insecure page, the browser issues a warning. And unfortunately, all the security warnings issued by the browser sound equally terrifying, whether they are really important or (as in this case) not. The message is merely about the page you get sent to after ordering, and your credit card and personal info are not going to be exposed. Many of us fear Internet identity theft, although on a daily basis we hand our credit cards to people in the retail and service industries across the world. Credit card companies know this, of course, and they understand that for the system to work and for individuals to use their cards freely, they must reduce consumer risk. As a measure against fraud, credit card companies limit your liability to a certain amount for any unauthorized use of your card, and most companies will waive even that fee. Companies selling merchandise and services online also realize that consumers need similar assurances that their personal information is safe and will not fall into the wrong hands. How can you tell if it is safe to buy? First you need to make sure you have a secure connection. It is easy to determine if your connection is secure; for example, when you use Netscape or Internet Explorer, a picture of a padlock appears in the lower section of your screen. A closed lock indicates a secure connection, which means that any information exchanged between you and the web site will be encrypted (scrambled). How does the closed-lock connection work? When you establish a secure connection, the downloaded web site sends a digital certificate to your browser. When this certificate arrives, it contains a public key, which functions as a one-way encryption device. The browser then uses this key to scramble your personal data before sending it over the Internet. Information encrypted with the public key cannot be decrypted without the corresponding private key, which only the merchant has. Without this exclusive, private key, your personal information cannot be read. 

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy the following notice explains the information we collect, how it is used, how it is safeguarded, and how to contact us if you have any concerns. 

#### What Information Is Collected: 

As part of the order process, the following information is collected from shoppers:    
Name, Shipping/Billing Address, Email address, Phone number
